A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, United States International Affairs Program (USIAP), Urban Poverty, Office Files of Marsha R. Hunter FA663
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, United States International Affairs Program (USIAP), Urban Poverty, Office Files of Marsha R. Hunter
1971-1982
Rockefeller Archive Center
Hunter, Marsha R.
Ford Foundation
FA663
1.31 Cubic Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Contains subject files.
Arrangement
As received.
Biographical / Historical
Marsha Hunter worked at the Ford Foundation for several years. She was an Assistant Program Officer for the Foundation's Nutrition Project, and then she became an Assistant Program Officer in the Urban Poverty Program.
- Subject Files, 1971-1982; I
  - Grantmakers in International Health, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Urban Poverty Program, 1982 (Box 1)
  - ECCO -- Newspaper clippings, RGA's, miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box 1)
  - ECCO, 1974 (Box 1)
  - ECCO (1/2), 1975 (Box 1)
  - ECCO (2/2), 1975 (Box 1)
  - ECCO, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Garza -- WIC Breastfeeding Project, 1980-1982 (Box 1)
  - Bard College Center, 1980 (Box 1)
  - South Bronx Development Corporation, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Planning Assistance Inc., 1980 (Box 1)
  - Pollitt, Ernesto -- Iron-deficiency grant, 1975-1980 (Box 1)
  - South Central Mississippi Rural Health Association, 1980 (Box 1)
  - David Pyle -- Consultant to FF Bangladesh Office, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - University of Arizona -- Breastfeeding among America Indians of the South West, 1980 (Box 1)
  - East Harlem Council on Human Services, 1980 (Box 1)
  - IFPRI, 1981 (Box 1)